<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AhnHn</string>

    <!--Salted Coffee-->
    <string name="scname">Ca Phe Muoi</string>
    <string name="scingredients">1 cup coffee, with milk and sugar if desired
        6 tablespoons heavy cream
        2 tablespoons sugar
        ½ teaspoon kosher salt
        ½ cup milk
        2 tablespoons cocoa powder
        ice
    </string>
    <string name="screcipe">
        Chill coffee in the refrigerator until ready to use.
        In a tall cup, add in the heavy cream, sugar, and salt. Whisk together with a mini whisk or electric frother until thick.
        Fill a chilled glass with ice. Pour in the ⅓ cup of milk, the chilled brewed coffee, and top with as much salted cream as you’d like!
        Dust with cocoa powder for garnish.
        Enjoy!
    </string>
    
    
    <!--The Cracked Coffee Latte-->
    <string name="cclattename">The Cracked Coffee Latte</string>
    <string name="cclatteingredients">
        1 cup milk of choice
        2 shots espresso
        1 tablespoon syrup or sweetener of choice
        ⅓ cup dark or milk chocolate
        ice cube
    </string>
    <string name="cclatterecipe">
        Melt the chocolate in a microwave-safe bowl in 30-second increments, stirring in between each time until fully melted.
        Pour the melted chocolate into a clear plastic cup, and coat the inside. Allow any excess to drip back into the bowl. Freeze the cup for about 10 minutes to set the chocolate.
        Assemble the drink: Fill the chocolate-coated cup to the top with ice cubes. Then pour in the sweetener, followed by the milk and freshly brewed espresso.
        Gently squeeze the cup to crack the chocolate mold, then give the drink a stir.
        Enjoy!
    </string>


    <!--Pot Coffee-->
    <string name="pcname">Cafecito De Olla</string>
    <string name="pcingredients">
        6 cups water(1.4 L)
        ½ cup coffee grounds(60 g)
        120 g piloncillo(120 g)
        2 whole cinnamon sticks
        2 whole star anise pods
        5 whole cloves
    </string>
    <string name="pcrecipe">
        In a medium pot, bring the water to a simmer over medium-low heat. Add the coffee grounds and piloncillo and stir for 2 minutes to dissolve the piloncillo. Add the cinnamon sticks, star anise pods, and cloves, and stir for 1 minute. Cover the pot and let the coffee simmer for 10 minutes.
        Strain the coffee and serve immediately.
        Enjoy!
    </string>



</resources>